All set here for you.
您这办好了
- Great, thank you.
- Next, please.
-好，谢谢
-来，下一位
Let's go.
走了
Applying for retirement.
办退休
Let me check your paperwork.
材料看一下
Did you bring your healthcare book?
保健本带了吗？
Your paperwork is incomplete.
您这个材料不齐呀
Why?
为啥？
This book is missing a stamp.
您这本上缺了个章
You need to get this stamp added.
您得把这个章补上
Our factory shut down years ago.
我们厂没多少年了
Where am I supposed to find someone to stamp it now?
我这不是找不着人盖这个章吗？
Just... just count the years.
您…您算算时间
Really... I've worked the full 30 years.
我真的…我够30年工龄了
Your situation is indeed quite unusual.
您这个情况确实比较特殊
Can you still contact Zhao Guangzhou, the agent from your old company?
您现在还能联系上 你们原单位的这个经办人赵广州吗？
Our factory's been gone for years.
我们厂子都没多少年了
I don't even know why he didn't stamp it back then.
我也不知道 他当时为啥不给我盖这个章
Where am I supposed to go find him now?
我现在上哪找他去呀？
Tell me, where am I supposed to find him?
你说我上哪找他去
What's wrong, Qiaoyun?
怎么的了，巧云？
What happened?
怎么的了？
Don't cry...
不哭…
I'm right here now.
我不过来了吗？
Let's talk this through calmly.
有话咱们好好说
I... I started at Hualin Steel on October 1st, 1986.
我…我1986年10月1号进的桦钢
I worked at the scale house operating the weighbridge.
在磅房管过磅
I left the plant on October 4th, 1998.
我1998年10月4号离的厂
I worked at Hualin Steel for 12 whole years.
我在桦钢整整工作了12年
In those 12 years, I didn't take a single day off.
这12年里面，我没有请过一天假
Why do I need someone else to prove now that I worked at Hualin Steel?
为什么现在还要让别的人来证明 我在桦钢工作过？
People reach their age, buses reach their stop.
人到岁数，车到站
We came here to file for retirement.
我们过来办退休
You keep giving us this excuse and that excuse.
你们这个那个，那个这个
What are you trying to pull?
想怎么的？
Don't worry, sir.
您别着急，大爷
We'll double-check her length of service again.
工龄的事我们再去核实一下
This won't affect her retiring on schedule.
这个事不会影响阿姨正常退休的
Rest assured.
您放心
Go on home first.
先回家
Here.
来
It's open. Eat up.
来了，吃吧
- Why did you spend money on this?
- Don't worry, eat up.
-你这…你花钱买这个干啥啊？
-没事，吃吧
You always say your heart feels bitter, so treat yourself to something sweet.
妳老说自己心里苦，整点甜的
My teeth can't take it anymore.
牙不行了
Nonsense.
妳净扯
If my teeth can manage, how can't yours?
我牙都行，妳牙还不行？
Eat.
吃
How... how do you open this?
这…这怎么开呢？
Don't rush.
先别着急啊
Take it easy.
稳当的
See this notch right here?
妳看这不有豁吗？
Pull right here.
撕这个
There you go.
妥了
Eat.
吃
I just feel so aggrieved.
我就是觉得憋屈
Laid off when I was so young.
年纪轻轻的就下岗了
Failed at everything since then.
干啥啥不成
At your age...
你这岁数的人了
...making a big scene and crying over this.
还因为这些个事又哭又闹的
Tell me, when will life ever get better?
你说这日子啥时候是个头啊？
It's alright.
没事
This will definitely get sorted out.
这事肯定能解决
Didn't they explain it to us just now?
人家不也给咱解释了吗？
Don't worry about it.
妳就踏实的吧
I keep causing trouble for you.
我这净给你添麻烦了
I wasted your driving time for making money.
耽误你出车挣钱了
Stop talking nonsense.
净扯用不着的
What waste?
耽误啥呀？
It's no trouble at all.
不耽误
Actually, there's something I wanted to ask you.
我正好有个事想问妳呢
What is it?
啥事？
Asking about someone.
跟妳打听个人
Didn't you use to work at Victoria back then?
以前妳不是 在那个维多利亚工作过吗？
Victoria, you know.
就是维多利亚
Victoria Entertainment Plaza.
娱乐广场
What do you mean by that?
你啥意思啊？
Just asking you about a person.
就是跟妳打听那个人啊
The girl who played the piano.
就是那个弹钢琴的
Named Shen Mo.
叫沈墨的
Were you close with her?
妳跟她熟不熟？
We crossed paths, but weren't close.
打过照面，不熟
She had a brother named Fu Weijun who's mute.
那她有个弟弟叫傅卫军，是个哑巴
Did you know about him?
妳知道不？
No recollection.
没印象
Help me think back.
妳帮我回忆回忆吧
Did you ever see that guy at Victoria back then?
妳当时在维多利亚见过这人没有啊？
I forgot all about those days. I...
那段我早就忘了，我这…
I can barely remember anything about Victoria.
维多利亚啥的我都记不清了
Take... take your time. No rush.
妳…妳帮我，妳不着急
Just try to think back slowly for me.
妳帮我慢慢想一想
Around 1997 or 1998.
就是1997、1998这两年的事
Wang Xiang.
王响
Has this been bothering you in your heart all along?
你是不是一直因为这个事 心里不痛快的？
I worked as a hostess.
我做过陪酒
If that makes you uncomfortable, just say so.
你要是不舒服，你就直说
Qiaoyun, I...
巧云，我…
Why would I be uncomfortable?
我不舒服啥呀？
I... I never even thought of it that way.
我…我压根…我都没往这上想过
Why would I... be uncomfortable?
我还…我还不舒服？
I've told you everything you asked.
你问我的事我都告诉你了
I don't know anything else.
再多我也不知道了
Fine... I'll head back on my own.
行了…我自己回去了
You eat it.
你吃吧
- I'm heading back.
- Wait, why?
-我回去了
-干啥？
Take it with you then.
那妳带着吃吧
It's too sweet, I can't eat it.
太甜，我吃不下
Then... let me give you a ride...
那…那我送妳…
No need...
不用…
I'll walk myself.
我自己走
What's going on with you? This got completely misunderstood.
妳这扯不扯？ 澈底整岔去了
This is a total misunderstanding.
这误会了这是
What a waste.
这浪费了
Next time you're free, let's grab some drinks.
等那个有空，到时候整点
Deal... I'll hit you up then.
成…到时候我约你啊
What's up? You took up dancing now?
怎么的？ 还跳上了？
Did that kid admit to hitting the person?
这小子承认他撞人这事了吧？
Well, the car is his, so he can't wriggle out of it.
反正车是他的，跑不了
But when it happened, where it happened, and who got hit...
但啥时间撞的 在啥地方撞的，撞的是谁
...even he can't explain clearly.
自己都说不清楚
Plus, the person who got hit hasn't reported it either.
这被撞那个人也不报案
Making it pretty tough to investigate.
这个事查起来有点困难
They can't share any more details.
其他的人家没法说了
We understand how it is.
这咱明白
Anything more would be breaking protocol.
再说属于违规
So slick.
真狡猾
What's the deal?
怎么的呀？
Isn't it just a simple hit-and-run?
不就一肇事逃逸吗？
Why are you so obsessed with it?
怎么这么上心呢？
You wouldn't understand.
你不懂
There's a story behind it, huh?
有故事吧
Or maybe it's just an accident.
那兴许就是个事故
Want one?
给你来一个不？
I'm telling you, I quit smoking.
我告诉你啊，我是把烟给戒了
But my mouth always feels so bland.
这嘴里老没味
Does this guy look familiar?
你看这人眼熟不？
Who is it?
谁呀？
The Hualin Medical University student.
桦医大学生
Don't you remember the dismemberment case?
碎尸案你不记得了？
Wasn't it this punk I beat up?
我干的不就这小子吗？
Isn't this her uncle?
这她那大爷吧
You beat him up real good back then.
你给人揍的，揍够呛
It wore me out, too.
我还累够呛呢
What was he doing here?
他来这干啥来了？
Maybe there really is a story here.
兴许这里头还真有故事
What kind of story?
有啥故事啊？
What's the hit-and-run kid named?
撞人那小子叫啥？
Shen Hui.
沉辉呀
- What about it?
- You sure?
-怎么的？
-准确吗？
Absolutely sure.
准确啊
Li Qun.
李群
Are you still in touch with him?
你还跟他有联系吗？
You held your breath all this time just to ask that?
憋了半天就问这个
Why would I be in touch with him?
我跟他联系啥？
He's a branch bureau chief now.
他都分局局长了
Out of my league.
咱也够不上啊
Listen to how bitter you sound.
你看你酸的
Look at yourself.
没看你这啥德行
A traffic cop with such a gloomy face.
一交警，脸这黑呢
Got plans tonight?
晚上有事吗？
Do you want me to have plans or not?
你是想让我有事啊，还是没事啊？
Let me buy you a nice meal.
我给你补补吧
Did you drive here?
开车没有啊？
No, do you have a ride?
没开呀，你有车呀
Hop on mine.
坐我车
There we go.
这不完了吗？
When did you get a new ride?
啥时候换的车呀？
Brand new?
新买的啊？
Don't touch that.
别弄
Hey, why are you messing with his ride?
不是，你动人车干啥呀？
A two-wheeler?
两轮的呀？
What's wrong with two wheels?
两轮怎么的？
Put on the helmet, quick.
赶紧的，拿着盔
This color actually suits me pretty well.
这颜色还挺适合我的
Right? Wearing pink makes you look vibrant.
可不？ 你戴粉的显得鲜亮
Sit back here?
坐这啊？
Hold on tight.
抱住了啊
Don't underestimate these two wheels.
别看这两轮
Faster than four.
比四轮快
Where do I put my feet?
踩哪呀？
Just drag 'em.
拖着吧
(Guiying's Flavorful BBQ)
（桂英风味烤肉）
It's hot.
热
Should we two just start eating first?
不行咱俩先吃吧？
Look what time it is.
这都几点了？
Is he even coming?
还能来吗？
I called him, would he dare not show up?
我叫他，他敢不来吗？
Are you hungry?
是不是饿了？
Drink some water.
喝水
Other people roast meat.
人家烤肉
We're sitting here burning charcoal.
咱俩在这烧炭
Looking like we're committing suicide.
整得跟自杀似的
How about I pay, okay?
要不行我请，成吗？
Yapping on and on...
叭叭…叭叭的
Will you give it a rest? We're on serious business here.
有完没完？ 这干正事呢
Are you that desperate for a meal?
你欠这顿饭呢？
Hey, I did all the work for you.
那不是事都给你干了
- Look at you.
- Why are you still the same as before?
-你看你
-怎么还原来那样呢？
Fine... can I go outside for a breath of fresh air then?
行…那我出去喘口气行吗？
Keep an eye out for him!
看着点人啊
Uncle.
叔
Should I put out the fire for you first?
我要不先把火给你灭了吧？
No need, aren't we sitting right here?
不用，不是人在这吗？
Just preheating.
先预个热
He'll be here in a minute.
一会人就来了
It's just I'm worried it'll burn out our grill.
主要我怕把我们家烧烤架给烧坏了
Are you Guiying?
妳是桂英吗？
If you're not Guiying, call Guiying over.
不是桂英，让桂英过来
What's your problem?
怎么的？
Upset over burning a little charcoal?
点点炭不乐意了？
Would I just burn charcoal without ordering meat?
我光点炭不点肉啊？
Is this how you run a business?
这怎么做生意呢？
Is your grill made of plastic?
妳家烧烤架是塑料做的
You're forcing me to lecture you, aren't you?
非让我說妳是不？
Kids these days...
这小姑娘
Chief Li.
李局
Captain Ma.
马队
My apologies.
不好意思啊
Got tied up with something urgent at the bureau.
刚才局里有点事，脱不开身
Of course you're busy, right?
你肯定忙啊，对不？
Not like us common folks.
不像我们老百姓
Nothing better to do.
闲得没事干
Come on, why say that?
你这话说哪去了？
It's all serving the people, just busywork.
也都是为人民群众服务，瞎忙
Look at you, look at your presence now.
你看你，你看现在这个派头
Really got the air of a bureau chief.
真有点局长那样了啊
Captain Ma.
马队啊
How come your hair's all white?
怎么头发都白了呀？
Still calling me Captain Ma?
还马队呢？
Old Ma.
老马
Waiter, menu please.
服务生，来，点菜
Scan QR code to order.
扫码点餐
Scan code? Talk about lazy.
扫码？ 这偷懒
Let me do it.
我来吧
How do you scan it?
怎么扫啊？
Let me...
我来…
- Let me handle it...
- What "let me, let me"?
-我来…
-什么你来你来的？
- I'll scan it.
- Can't I treat you to a meal?
-我来扫
-我还不能请你吃个饭呢？
- Why insist on...
- Alright...
-怎么还就…
-行了…
You're the guest of honor today.
请的就是你
- Alright, stop squabbling, Old Ma.
- Let me... my treat...
-行了，别拉扯，老马
-我来…我请…
Fine, go ahead.
行，你来吧
I'll just order randomly.
我随便点啊
Beef, pork belly, grilled chicken hearts...
牛肉、五花肉、烤鸡心
How many years has it been since we last met?
咱俩多少年没见了？
I heard you're doing great at square dancing these days.
我听人家说你现在广场舞跳挺好啊
What square dancing? Who's spreading nonsense?
什么广场舞？ 听谁胡说呢？
Latin dance, you know?
拉丁，你知道吧？
It's pure style.
就是帅
I'm the coolest guy in the world.
全世界我最帅
Latin dance...
拉丁…
Drink some water.
喝水
- There's...
- Waiter!
-这有…
-服务员
No cups here.
没有杯子
Do we have to scan a code for cups too?
这杯子也扫码啊？
Old Ma.
老马
Anyone else coming?
还有谁呀？
Your skewers smell fantastic.
你这小味挺绝啊
How many years have you been grilling?
烤多少年了？
Five or six years, big brother.
五、六年了，大哥
Is that so?
是吗？
Rush my ten skewers a bit, I'm in a hurry.
我那十串稍微快点，着急啊
You got it!
好咧
Where's your chili powder?
你辣椒在哪呢？
Right here.
搁这呢
Sprinkle extra.
多撒点
My chili powder is extra spicy.
我这辣椒可辣呀
Don't worry, he's from Sichuan.
没事，他是四川的
Here you go...
来呀…
All ready, enjoy.
这好了，来
What's wrong?
怎么了？
Look at Mr. Bureau Chief.
这局长当的
No one serving food onto your plate, so you forgot how to eat?
没人给夹菜，不会吃饭了？
Why am I so glad to see you?
我见你怎么那么高兴呢？
Eat up.
吃啊
Earlier you kept complaining you were starving.
刚才饿饿饿的
From waiting so long.
等的
I'm past being hungry.
饿过劲了
Come on... let's have a drink.
来…那喝酒
- Cheers.
-来
Let me pour for Chief Li.
我给李局倒上
Can't drink...
不能喝…
Regulations prohibit it.
有规定
Aren't you off the clock?
这不下班了吗？
Who here hasn't been a cop?
谁没当过警察呀？
- Come on...
- Old Ma.
-来吧…
-老马
- Be understanding...
- Come on.
-多体谅…
-来吧
Really can't drink, can't do it.
真不能喝，不能喝
Captain Ma, it's understandable.
马队，能理解
He's Chief Li now.
人家现在是李局了
Not like us. Be more understanding.
跟咱们不一样，多体谅
Why so full of snide remarks? What's your problem?
说话夹枪带棒的，干嘛呢？
Then I... come on...
那我…来…
I'll drink with you, cheers.
我跟你喝，来
What are you doing?
你要干嘛呀？
Aren't you riding a scooter?
你不是骑着车吗？
Aren't you afraid of getting pulled over by cops?
不怕警察逮你呀？
And you're a traffic cop yourself?
还交警呢还？
Have some meat.
烤肉
To be honest...
说实话啊
Meeting old leaders and colleagues today...
今天能见着老领导、老同事…
- My mood...
- Chicken gizzards!
-心情…
-鸡胗
...I feel truly delighted.
我这心情是愉悦的
Tell you what.
这样
I'll toast with tea instead of alcohol, fair?
我以茶代酒，行不？
Is that alright?
可以吗？
Um... Li Qun.
那个…李群
Let me interrupt you for a second.
我先插你一句啊
If we're talking about opening remarks...
要说开场
...it has to be Captain Ma.
还得是马队
What do you think?
你觉得呢？
Me, opening remarks?
我开场啊？
Then I'll say a few words.
那我开场吧
We're all brothers here.
都是兄弟
Old Ma.
老马
Did you ask me out because something's up?
找我是不是有啥事啊？
If there's something, just speak plainly.
有啥事你直说得了
Really nothing.
真没啥事
What could there be?
能有啥事？
Can't a simple dinner just be a dinner?
你吃个饭还吃出事来了？
As long as it's reasonable...
只要合情合理
...I won't drag my feet if I can help.
能办我肯定不拖着
Then I'll speak up.
那我就说啊
Back then, didn't you interrogate Fu Weijun in his case?
当年傅卫军这案子不是你审的吗？
Old Ma.
老马
I was young and impetuous back then.
当年我是年轻气盛
To be honest, in my heart...
说实话这个事在我心里
...I've never truly gotten over it.
我到现在都没过去
That's not what I'm referring to.
说的不是这事
It's fine, it's really nothing.
我说没事，没事吧
Back then in Songhe, Fu Weijun...
这傅卫军当时在松河
...didn't he have an intentional assault charge?
不是有一个故意伤害吗？
You should know about it.
你应该知道啊
I know.
我知道
Fu Weijun broke someone's arm back in Songhe.
傅卫军当时在松河把人胳膊给砸折了
It was already combined into his prison sentence back then.
当年就已经合并执行在刑期了
Sui Dong, who was with him, got sentenced too.
跟他一起那个隋东也判了
What are you trying to say?
你想说啥呀？
This kid is named Shen Hui.
这小子叫沉辉
Now he drives an illegal taxi in Hualin.
在桦林现在开黑车
A few days ago...
前几天
...he got detained for a hit-and-run with cloned plates.
套牌肇事给拘了
The victim he hit never reported it to police.
被他撞的这人一直没报警
And we can't locate the person now.
现在人也找不着
I called the prison.
我给这监狱打过电话
I found out Fu Weijun died in prison earlier this month.
我就了解到这傅卫军 在这个月初就死在这监狱里了
Is there any connection between these two things?
这两个事情有啥联系吗？
I don't know what connection there is, either.
我就是不知道有啥联系
I need to take a look at the 1998 case files.
我得看看这1998年这案子的卷宗
Come on...
来…
Come on.
来
Here.
This matter...
这个事
...you've got to help me with.
你得帮我啊
Old Ma.
老马
I know you haven't moved on from this case.
我知道这个案子你没过去
Just like me—I haven't moved on either.
咱俩一样，我也没过去
But non-police personnel cannot access these case files.
但是非警务人员不能接触这个卷宗
You know how it works.
这你懂
If you get any leads in the future...
我希望以后有什么线索
...I hope you can provide them directly to the police.
你可以直接提供给警方
Leave the actual legwork to us officers.
动手的事交给我们警察就行了
Look at him.
你瞅瞅
Laying on the official jargon.
小官腔打的
Really treating me like ordinary civilian folk.
还真把我当人民群众了
I was playing this routine 20 years ago.
就你这套，我20年前就玩过了
Back when I was captain, you kid...
我是队长的时候，你小子…
Just tell me straight, will you help or not?
你就说帮不帮吧
We're done for.
完了
Anything else is fine.
别的都可以
But viewing the files...
但是看卷宗
...is out of the question.
不行
It violates regulations.
违反纪律
Li Qun.
李群
This matter is very important to me.
这件事对我很重要
This matter is very important to me, too.
这事对我也很重要
- Let me drop this.
- Stop talking about it.
-这事就别聊
-别聊了
Eat up...
吃…
Eat it all.
都吃了
Right, eat some meat...
对，吃肉…
Don't let good food go to waste.
不能耽误了饭呀
Here, Chief Li.
来，李局
These are skewers I specially ordered outside.
这是我在外边特意点的串
Give 'em a try.
尝尝
Give me one.
给我一个
I'm afraid of tough meat.
我怕老
Have something tender.
吃点嫩的
The Hualin Steel dismemberment case files have been pulled.
桦钢碎尸案的卷宗已经调出来了
Shen Hui is at the police station now.
沉辉现在在派出所
Interrogation starts right away.
马上提审
They're already on it.
已经去了
Surveillance footage of the hit-and-run has been retrieved too.
肇事逃逸的监控也已经拿到了
Everyone's present.
人都到齐了
Captain Ma.
马队啊
Not to rain on your parade...
不是我打击你啊
...how are you even going to piece this case together?
你这案子怎么捋啊？
The guy is dead. Who are you going to ask?
人都死了，你问谁去？
Prison No. 2 is in Fengshan District, right?
那二监是凤山区吧？
Yeah.
对呀
Then...
那…
When an inmate at Prison No. 2 dies...
二监那犯人死了
...where do they cremate them?
在哪火化呀？
Probably Fengshan Funeral Home.
凤山殡仪馆吧
(Hualin Fengshan Funeral Home)
（桦林凤山殡仪馆）
Your staff works way too carelessly.
你们这工作也太不严谨了
How could you even misplace an urn?
这骨灰盒都能给整没了
Exactly!
就是啊
Weijun was our close relative.
那卫军是咱实在亲戚
Just because he committed a crime...
妳不能说人犯错误了
...you can't leave not even a handful of his ashes!
那灰也不给留一把啊
What kind of operation is this?
什么玩意？
No smoking allowed here. Fire prohibited.
这不让抽烟，禁止烟火
You ignore all those people burning joss paper outside.
外面那么多烧纸的妳不管
Doesn't that big smokestack outside puff smoke every day?
那外面大烟囱不天天冒烟吗？
And you talk about prohibiting fire?
还禁止烟火？
Stop nagging me here!
你们别跟我在这啰唆了啊
Can ashes just be picked up by anyone?
骨灰是能随便领走的吗？
Whoever took them definitely went through standard procedures.
那能领走的，走的肯定是正常程序啊
You don't even know who took them, and you call that standard?
谁领走都不知道，还正常呢？
Help us check who claimed them.
帮我们查查吧，谁领走的
Just tell us, and that'll be that.
告诉我们一嘴不就完了吗？
You don't have any ID or proof of identity.
你们啥身分证明都没有
How can I check for you?
怎么给你们查？
No proof of identity?
我们没身分？
This is a retired police officer!
这是退休的公安干警
Former Captain of Criminal Investigation, Hualin Public Security!
桦林市公安局老刑警队队长
Captain Ma, show her your retirement badge.
马队，退休证给她看看
It's on me.
在身上
Did you bring it?
带没带呀？
Wasn't it with you just now?
刚才不是还在你那吗？
It's with you.
在你那
Just check it quickly.
妳就快点查吧
Once Captain Ma flashes his badge...
一会马队一亮证
...even your funeral home director will have to come out in person to greet him, got it?
你们殡仪馆馆长 都得亲自出来接待，知道不？
The current police chief was promoted by him!
现在的公安局长是他提拔的
In your back pocket, for sure.
在屁兜上，肯定的
No back pocket.
没屁兜
Alright... stop digging.
行了…别翻了
Found it. There's a record here.
我查着了，这有纪录
Claimed by a relative.
领取人是亲属
Registered under the name Shen Dongliang.
登记名是沉栋梁
When was it claimed?
啥时候领走的？
(Changsong Gardens)
（长松园）
Here.
来
Ten yuan.
十块钱
Give me a receipt.
开个票
Issue one for last time too.
把上回那个也给我开了
What last time?
啥上回啊？
I came by a couple of days ago.
头两天我来过一次
Paid, but forgot to get the receipt.
交钱了，忘开票了
What date was that?
几号来的呀？
Forgot the exact date.
几号忘了
Look up plate Hua-AW357F.
你查查桦AW357F
Right here.
这呢
Wait, this receipt was already issued to you.
不对啊，这票给你开过了
Really?
是吗？
See right here.
这啊
Then give me this copy.
那你这票给我呀
Pretty meticulous, huh.
还挺严谨的
What are we having for lunch?
咱中午吃点啥呀？
You two pick, my treat.
你俩挑吧，我请客
Then let's eat something good.
那就吃点好的吧
Once we're full this time, keep a sharp stakeout for me.
这回吃饱了，都给我好好蹲守啊
When we get inside later, neither of you say a word.
一会要是进了屋啊，你们俩都别插嘴
I'll do all the asking.
主要我问
Take it easy.
你悠着点吧
Don't go pulling a muscle again.
你再扯着裆
Who's in better shape...
这谁身体好啊
...becomes clear as day when you compare.
一比就比出来了
Give me a break.
你可拉倒吧
You're just full of hot air after overeating.
你那就吃多了撑的
Why is she throwing such a huge temper?
这怎么生这么大气呀这是？
Brother-in-law, no wonder she's angry.
姐夫啊，难怪人生气
You basically chatter aimlessly without knowing how to talk to women.
就你基本属于那个不会聊瞎聊
You completely botched the conversation.
那嗑让你给唠得稀碎
You're lucky she didn't smash a thermos over your head.
人没拿暖瓶砸你算你运气好
One widowed, one on the verge of divorce.
一个丧偶，一个快离了
Don't try lecturing me on romantic relationships!
在感情这方面就别给我上课了啊
Women...
这女人吧
...especially women of a certain age...
尤其是上点年龄的女人
You gotta rub her the right way first before bringing up business.
你得先捋毛，毛捋顺了你再说事
You have to listen to Old Man Ma on this.
这你得听老马头的
He's got heaps of experience in this department.
这方面他老有经验了
- I'm not out of breath.
- Come on, Old Man Ma.
-不喘
-来，老马头
Watch how I handle it.
你看我怎么捋
A whole string of missed calls.
一串未接
What's this?
这啥呀？
Call her right back then.
你再折过去啊
Alright, alright...
来，行了…
Let me steady you.
我扶着你点
Let me see.
你给我看看
Let me take a look...
我看看啊
If you keep calling back now, it's harassment.
你这在过去就是骚扰
You need to send her a text message.
你得给人发个讯息
Say it like this:
这么说啊
"Yun...
“云啊
I was wrong, boo-hoo..."
我错了，呜呜”
Add an emoji.
来个表情
"I have no right to offer excuses...
“我没有资格跟妳解释
I just don't want you to stay mad at me."
我就不想让妳一直生气”
Add one more sentence:
加一句
"It breaks my heart."
“我会心疼”
We've got a true master here!
高手在这呢
"Give me a chance tonight...
“晚上给我个机会
...to take you out for dinner...
请妳吃个饭
...and apologize to you in person."
当面向妳请罪”
See, hit send?
你看，发不发？
Sent.
发了
Get ready to get chewed out.
等着挨怼吧
Good luck.
加油
See, all that square dancing paid off!
广场舞没白跳吧
I'll tell you two one more time:
我再跟你俩说一次啊
It's not square dancing, it's Latin dance!
不是广场舞，拉丁啊
- Get down... don't look...
- Is it them?
-下来…别瞅…
-是不是啊？
- What are you running for?
- Biaozi...
-跑啥呀？
-彪子…
Relax, it's nothing.
放松点，没事
They entered the hallway.
进楼道了
Alright.
行
- Hurry.
- Okay.
-快
-好
This is the one.
是这家
Right here.
就这家
Knock! What are you waiting for? Waiting to be served?
敲啊，等啥呢？ 等上菜呢？
Anyone home?
屋里有人吗？
Hello.
你好
We're from Property Management.
我是物业的
Downstairs reported a leak coming from your place.
楼下反映你们家漏水了
We came over to inspect and repair.
我们过来检修一下
Please cooperate.
请你们配合
Knock!
敲啊
Open up, Property Management!
开门，物业的
Is it this unit? Are you sure you got it right?
是这屋吗？ 整明白了吗？
Just knock when I tell you to.
让你敲你就敲
Young man, you've got the wrong door.
小伙子，敲错了
Over here, I'm the one who called.
这边，我打的电话
No mistake, it's this unit.
没错，就这家
Then after you finish fixing theirs...
那等你们给他们修完了
...could you come fix mine?
能不能上我家修修？
I can wait a bit.
我等会也行
What's broken at your place?
你们家哪坏了？
The kitchen pipe is leaking.
厨房水管漏了
Go back inside then, someone will be there shortly.
那妳回去吧，一会人就来了
I can just wait right here.
我就在这等着也行
Do you know how to fix it?
你会修吗？
I suppose I do.
那就会吧
Can you figure it out?
能整明白吗？
Is this harder to repair than a train locomotive?
这比火车还难修啊？
So it was your place that had the leak?
原来是你们家漏水了呀？
We really got the wrong door.
还真整错了
Do you know this neighbor? Is their surname Shen?
妳认识这家吗？ 是姓沉吗？
Here, phone light.
来，手机
Shine it here.
照亮，来
If you can't figure it out, let's bail.
整不明白撤吧
Stop showing off.
别逞能了
Hey, mister, come on inside.
那人，你进来吧
It's cool in here.
这凉快
The two of them can handle this small job.
这点活他俩就能干
It's completely ruined.
这完蛋了
Ruined?
完蛋了？
Ma'am...
大姐呀
This fixture is loose.
这玩意松了
It leaks no matter how you tighten it.
怎么拧都漏水
What should we do then?
那怎么办呢？
Where's the main shut-off valve?
总阀在哪呢？
On the sixth floor...
在六楼…
Do this:
妳这样啊
I'll go shut off the main valve.
我去把那个总阀给它关上
First make sure it stops leaking.
首先保证不漏水
Then buy a small valve, install it, and you'll be set.
完了买个小阀，把它安上就妥了啊
This is Master Biao here.
这是那个彪师傅
Find a few dry rags...
妳找几块干抹布
...and let him mop the floor clean from inside to out.
让他从里到外把地擦干净的
What mop the floor clean?
我擦啥干净的我呀？
I don't even do housework at my own home!
我在家我都不干活
Did I come here to do manual labor for you?
我跑这跟你干活来了啊？
Ma'am, do you live all by yourself?
不是，大姨，妳家就妳一个人呀？
Where are your kids?
子女呢？
Living out of town.
在外地呢
Get me a few dry rags then.
妳给我整几块干抹布吧
Okay.
好
What's the point of raising kids?
你说养孩子那玩意有啥用
Better off raising pigeons.
还不如养鸽子呢
Or even raising a dog.
养狗也行
Don't just stand there like a pole.
你别杵那了
Come give me a hand!
过来搭把手啊
Where's all that energy you had downstairs?
刚才楼下那劲头呢？
Quit yapping.
别叭叭了
Get to work, quick!
赶紧干啊
Spending all your energy in the wrong places every day.
一天那劲用不到正地方
Room 305, right?
305是不？
Yeah, over at 305.
对，305那边
Conscience kicked in?
良心发现了？
Rag.
布
Give me one.
来一块
Wring it into this basin.
往这盆里整
Your unit reported a broken pipe, right?
你家报修水管是吧？
It's all fixed. What took you so long?
都弄好了，怎么才来呢？
Thank you!
谢谢啊
Who are you two?
你俩谁呀？
We're from Property Management.
我俩物业的
Aren't we Property Management?
这不物业的吗？
Fine, you guys handle it.
行，你们弄吧
- Hold on...
- Who are you two?
-等会
-你俩谁呀？
Hello.
你好
We're also from Property Management.
我们也是物业的
Do you know them?
你认识吗？
If you two are Property Management, then who are we?
你们俩物业的，那我们俩谁呀？
- We're new hires.
- Wait... hold on a second.
-新来的
-不是…先等一下
New hires?
新来的？
You look like you're pushin' 60!
这我看你得有60了吧
Re-hired after retirement?
返聘呢？
Hey, watch your mouth!
不是，你怎么说话呢？
Mind your manners.
注意点分寸啊
Ma'am, check if any of your belongings are missing.
阿姨，看看东西丢没
Lately there are scammers in our complex targeting seniors.
最近咱小区有几个骗子专门骗老人
Multiple cases already, I'm telling you.
好几起了，我告诉妳
Seeing how old you guys are...
我这看你都老大不小的了
...how can you team up to scam an elderly person's money?
怎么能合伙骗老人家钱呢？
Who scammed money?
谁骗钱了？
How dare you talk like that?
你怎么说话呢？
- Stop fighting...
- Do you know who he is?
-吵…
-你知道他谁不？
Fine... don't say another word.
行…别说了
Truth be told...
实话实说
...we're police officers, here on a case.
我们警察，来办案的
Why didn't you say you're Emperor Kangxi...
你怎么没说你是康熙呢？
...out inspecting in disguise?
来微服私访的呢？
What's that supposed to mean?
你啥意思啊你？
Nothing. Come back to the Property Management office with us and clear this up.
没啥意思，跟我回物业把事情说清楚
Don't get physical!
别上手啊
- What's with this attitude?
- Are you crazy?
-什么态度呢？
-你有病吧？
- So what if you're Property Management?
- Don't be impulsive!
-物业的怎么的了？
-别冲动
- Property Management?
- What's going on here?
-物业的？
-怎么的啦这是？
- What are you trying to do?
- Then I'm calling the police.
-要干啥？
-那我报警
- I'm calling the police!
- Call them then... you think I'm scared?
-我报警
-你报…我怕你？
- Fine, calling the police!
- Go ahead and call!
-好，我报警
-你报警
No need to call, I'll go with you.
不用报，我跟你们走
- Let go of me!
- You let go of me!
-你给我撒开
- You let go!
- Alright, everybody let go.
-你撒
-行，都撒开
- How about my leaking pipe?
- What kind of attitude is this?
-我这水管怎么整啊？
-什么态度啊？
Fix her water pipe properly first!
给人把水管修好了
Don't you know what we came here to do?
不知道自己来干啥的？
- Let's go.
- You take him back first.
-走
-你先带他回去
What took you so long earlier?
早干啥去了？
The work was almost finished.
活都快干完了
Let's... let me go.
走…走了
Don't push me, I can walk myself.
你别推我，我自己能走
- When told to move, move!
- Tough talker on your home turf.
-让你走你就走
-炕头上能耐
Would it kill you to keep your mouth shut for once?
少说两句能死啊？
I'd go crazy.
能疯
If you hadn't pulled this mess today, would we be in this spot?
这不是你今天整这破事，能这样啊？
If that kid hadn't held me back...
那小子他不拦着我
...I tell you, I would've beaten him to a pulp.
我跟你说我脾气废了他
I...
我…
Anyone here?
有人吗？
Is anyone home?
有没有人？
What happened to you?
妳怎么的了？
Feeling any better?
好点没？
This...
这…
You two again?
又是你们俩呀？
What happened to him?
怎么了他这是？
Seasonal nausea—scared half to death.
季节性反胃，被吓的
Come over here.
过来吧
Calling you.
叫你呢
- Me?
- Yes.
-我？
-对
Don't hand that to me!
你别给我呀
Just throw it.
扔一下
Name?
姓名？
Wang Xiang.
王响
"Xiang" as in "resounding".
“响亮”的“响”
You went in by yourself?
就你自个进去的？
Right, weren't the two of them taken away by property management?
对，他俩不是被物业带走了吗？
(Qiaoyun)
（巧云）
My phone's ringing, can I answer it?
我来电话了，能不能接一下？
What do you think?
你觉着呢？
Officer...
警察同志
...just let him take the call.
你就让他接吧
It's not easy for seniors to find love.
老年人搞个对象不容易
Did anyone tell you to talk?
让你说话了吗？
Sit straight.
你坐好了
In a moment we'll talk about you impersonating police and scamming.
一会再聊你们冒充警察诈骗的事
Read this statement yourself to see if it's accurate.
你自己看看这个笔录属不属实
If there are no issues, you can sign.
如果没什么问题就可以签字了
Didn't that bureau chief carry your bag back in the day?
这局长不当年给你拎过包吗？
Drop his name to them!
跟他们提提人啊
If you're so capability, go say it yourself.
你厉害你说去
Dropping the ball when it matters most.
关键时候掉链子
Can't afford the embarrassment.
丢不起这人
Nothing serious.
没啥事
Bring that guy in the back inside for me.
把那个最里边那人给我叫进来
Come out for a moment.
你出来一下
Calling you.
叫你呢
Drop his name!
提提人啊
Look at this big desk.
你看这大桌子
Way more impressive than back then.
比那会可气派多了啊
Have a seat, Captain Ma.
坐吧，马队
Extra handsome.
特帅
What's the situation?
啥情况呀？
You and the two outside...
你还有外面那俩
...what are you trying to do?
想干啥呀？
Impersonating property management, trespassing into private homes, tampering with crime scenes...
假扮物业，私闯民宅，破坏现场
Playing *Mission: Impossible*?
《不可能的任务》啊？
Didn't we investigate our way right here?
这不也是查到这了吗？
Why are you getting so worked up?
你还上火了？
How could I not get worked up?
怎么不上火呢？
What are you even investigating?
你查啥呀？
What kind of criminal could you guys catch?
啥罪犯能让你们查着呀？
If you guys solve it all, should we cops just sit around twiddling our thumbs?
都让你们查着了，我们吃干饭吧
Is that what you mean?
是这个意思吗？
Weren't we trying to untangle a lead to hand over to you?
这不是想捋出个线头来，交给你吗？
Well, thank you so much!
我谢谢你啊
Do you want to investigate Shen Dongliang?
你是不是想查沉栋梁？
18 years ago, union official at Songhe Textile Factory No. 2.
18年前松河纺织二厂的工会干部
Shen Mo's uncle.
沈墨的亲大爷
And effectively her adoptive father.
也算是她的养父
The hit-and-run driver with cloned plates is his son, Shen Hui.
肇事逃逸的套牌车司机 就是他儿子沉辉
What else did you find out?
还查着啥了？
Didn't I tell you last time?
我上次不跟你说过了吗？
Even if I found out something, I couldn't tell you.
我查着啥，我也不能告诉你呀
Let you old gents keep shining in your golden years?
接着让你们老几位发挥余热去啊？
Look at the three of you.
你说你们仨
What if something happens to you?
出点啥事怎么办呢？
How do we clean up the mess?
怎么收场？
How do I answer to your families?
我怎么跟你们家属交代？
You're throwing off the rhythm of our investigation.
你们打乱我们的侦破节奏
How do you answer to me?
你怎么向我交代？
Haven't even said anything...
这啥也没说呢
...and you're already flying off the handle.
就激动上了
Fine.
好
Chief Li.
李局
Don't... don't call me Chief Li.
别…别李局
Xiao Li.
小李
Captain Ma.
马队
I have just one request for you.
我就拜托你一件事
What request?
什么事？
Stop causing trouble.
别捣乱
How did it go? Did you drop his name?
怎么样啊？ 提人没？
What did he say?
怎么说的？
Didn't say much.
没说啥
Just casual chitchat.
就随便瞎聊聊嘛
Just wait and see.
等着吧
Coming this late, really.
这么晚才来，真是
Heading out?
要出去啊？
No.
没有啊
Teacher Wu, why are you coming over so late?
吴老师，你怎么这么晚过来了？
My lower back started acting up again today.
今天这腰又闹起来了
Hurting badly.
疼得厉害
Is it convenient?
方不方便？
Sure...
方便…
Come on in.
你进来吧
Brought you some mandarins.
给妳带点橘子
Thank you.
谢谢啊
No problem...
没事…
You haven't eaten yet, right?
妳还没吃饭吧？
Not yet.
没吃呢
Neither have I.
我也没吃呢
Got takeout from the wonton shop.
从馄饨店打包了点
Thought I'd eat at home.
寻思回家吃
Packed too much by mistake—two orders.
一包给包多了，两盒
Want to eat together?
要不一起吃？
We can do the massage after eating.
吃完了再按
Alright, after we eat.
行，吃完了再按
Here, have a seat inside.
来，你里边坐
This one has cilantro.
这份有香菜
This one doesn't.
这份没有
I remembered you don't eat cilantro, right?
我记得妳是不吃香菜是吧？
I don't eat cilantro.
我不吃香菜
Isn't that perfect timing?
这不巧了吗？
Here.
来
Thanks.
好
Dig in.
吃吧
Is it still hot?
还热乎吗？
Captain Ma...
马队…
Then...
那…
...what's our next step?
下一步咱们怎么办呢？
Next step? Leave it to the police.
怎么办？ 交给警察吧
They will give us an answer.
人家会给交代的
I'm off.
走了
Where are you going, Captain Ma?
上哪啊，马队？
Let me give you a ride.
捎上你吧
Really stop calling me Captain Ma from now on.
以后真别叫马队了
I haven't been a cop for a long time.
早就不是警察了
Head back, Brother-in-law.
回去吧，姐夫
You go on ahead.
你自己走吧
I'll take a stroll.
我溜达遛达
Where are you taking a stroll in the middle of the night?
那大半夜上哪遛达呀？
Going for a massage?
按摩去呀？
Chief Li.
李局
Shen Dongliang has multiple stab wounds on his back.
沉栋梁背后有多处刀伤
The killer likely attacked him from behind while he was cooking.
凶手应该是趁他炒菜的时候 从背后下的手
Oxygen supply for his wife, Zhao Jing, was also unplugged.
他爱人赵静的氧气电源也被拔了
No property or valuables were stolen from the scene.
现场没有发现财物丢失
Shen Dongliang appears to have put up a fight.
沉栋梁应该是有过反抗的
We found skin tissue under his fingernails.
我们在他的指甲里发现了皮肤组织
Sent off for DNA testing already.
已经送去做DNA检测了
Also, in Shen Dongliang's house, we found private letters belonging to Fu Weijun.
另外，我们在沈栋梁家 找到了一些傅卫军的私人信件
He probably retrieved them from the prison.
应该是他从监狱里领回来的
The return address on all these letters is the same location.
这些信的通讯地址都是一个地方的
We checked it out.
我们查过了
Hongyan Sand & Gravel Plant in Genieng Banner, Inner Mongolia.
是内蒙古格宁旗的鸿雁砂石厂
The contact person is named Yin Hong.
联系人叫殷红
Information provided by Inner Mongolia police:
内蒙警方提供的资讯
...this Yin Hong purchased a long-distance bus ticket on October 19th.
这个殷红在10月19号 曾经购买过长途车票
The bus was bound for Hualin.
这趟车就是来桦林的
Issue an assistance request to locate Yin Hong.
发协查，找到这个殷红
Chief Li.
李局
Do you think those suspicious points in Fu Weijun's original confession...
你觉得傅卫军当时口供里那些疑点
...might be related to this?
会不会就跟这件事有关系？
What kind of lousy disc is this?
这啥破碟呀？
Lagging like a tractor.
卡得跟拖拉机似的
Boss, swap the disc!
老板，换片
Why is it still fucking stuttering?
这怎么还他妈突突？
Stuttering all afternoon, isn't that annoying?
突突一下午，闹不闹腾？
Swap it out!
换片
What's wrong with this disc?
这片怎么的了？
It's not lagging.
不卡呀
What's your problem?
怎么的呀？
Do I only get a swap if it stutters?
卡才能换片是吗？
Can't you play one of *those* movies?
你就不能放一点那种片吗？
Doesn't your blackboard outside say there's special feature added today?
你外面黑板上不都写着 今天有加片吗？
Special features gotta wait until after nine o'clock.
加片也得等九点后啊
It's... it's not even fully dark yet.
这…这天都没黑透呢
Did I fucking come here to watch movies or look at the sky?
我他妈是来看录像，还是来看天的？
Put on *Sex and Zen* for me, move it!
给我放个《肉蒲团》，赶紧的
I only smoke State Express 555.
我只抽三五
Go buy me a pack.
给我买去
Giving you too much face, aren't I?
给你脸了是吧？
I'll go buy it.
我买去
That's fucking more like it.
这他妈还差不多
Fuck.
操
You're leaving?
走了？
Refunded your ticket?
票退了啊？
We meet again.
又见面了
Forgot.
忘了
You're not just mute.
你不光哑巴
You're fucking deaf too.
还他妈聋
(Video Screening Room)
（录像厅）
Fuck!
操
Fuck, beat him!
我操，干他
Get him!
干他
Minus 68.
减68
Minus 32.
减32
Minus 85 equals 325.
减85等于325
That's all of it.
就这些
And that's after I swallowed my pride to pull strings for you.
这还是哥覥老脸给妳争取来的
You quit just like that without warning.
妳說妳这说辞职就辞职
Does big brother not have to spend time and effort finding someone to replace you?
那哥找人不也得费点时间 费点力吗？
You gotta take some responsibility.
那妳得担点责
Come to big brother if you ever need anything.
有啥事找哥啊
When is your fried starch jelly shop opening?
妳那煎粉店啥时候开业啊？
Soon, just looking for a venue.
快了，正找地呢
Once it's up and running, all of you come eat.
等开起来，妳们都去吃
On the house.
免费
Did you hit a jackpot recently?
妳最近是发什么财了？
Shen Mo.
沈墨
Why are you dodging me? I was looking for you.
躲什么呀？ 我正找妳呢
What's the rush? I have real business to talk with you.
着啥急呀？ 我有正事跟妳說
Let's go.
走
President Lu said...
卢总说
...since we're all so familiar by now...
反正咱们都那么熟了
...he wants to pick a day for the two of us to go party with him at his hotel.
他想找一天让咱俩跟他去酒店玩去
You bastard.
混蛋
You're a fucking bastard...
妳他妈混蛋…
You fucking bastard!
妳他妈混蛋
Fuck, are you ever gonna stop?
他妈的，妳还没完没了还
Did I ever harm you?
我害過妳吗？
Why are you treating me like this?
妳为啥这么对我？
You were the one who got drunk yourself.
是妳自己喝醉了
Is that my fault?
怨得着我吗？
Besides...
再说了
...I'm creating an opportunity for you.
我是在给妳创造机会
How many girls are desperate to cling to President Lu?
多少人想往卢总身上贴
And he doesn't even spare them a glance.
人家还看不上呢
Don't go acting like you're so pure and noble.
妳也别觉着妳有多清高
I drink with clients to make money.
我陪人喝酒赚钱
You play the piano to make money.
妳弹钢琴赚钱
It's all for money.
都是为了钱
You're no better than me.
不比我多啥
Think it over carefully.
妳好好想想
I'll wait for your answer.
等妳信啊
Surrender yet?
服没服？
Fuck!
我操
Lisping freak.
大舌头
Can't you sign language?
你不是会比划吗？
Come on, translate for your mute brother.
来，给你哑巴兄弟翻译翻译
Fuck.
操
Got a filthy mouth, don't you?
你嘴挺脏呀
Erfei.
二肥
Here, brother.
来，哥
Still cursing?
还骂吗？
Fuck your mother!
操了你妈
I...
我…
Now you can speak.
会说话了
The mute guy has something to say.
哑巴有话要说
Still acting tough with me?
还跟我硬？
Hualin Steel isn't a place for you two.
桦钢不是你俩待的地
Don't ever come back.
以后别来了
- Add extra ice.
- Brother.
-多放点冰啊
-哥
Don't call me brother yet.
先别叫哥
You haven't shown up for work in days—where were you?
你这好几天不上班，干啥去了？
Have you seen Shen Mo?
你瞅见沈墨了吗？
Did you come here to work or to play house?
你是来上班的还是来过家家的？
Are... are you paying my salary?
是…是你给我开工资吧？
Between your absenteeism and tardiness this month...
你这个月连旷工带迟…
I'm talking to you!
我跟你说话呢
Hello?
喂？
Please page 9532657.
帮我呼9532657
Yes, leave a message.
对，留言
"I was wrong that day.
“那天是我不对
Where are you now?
妳现在在哪？
I'll come find you right away."
我马上去找妳”
What happened between you and that college girl?
妳跟那大学生怎么的了？
Nothing, just messing around.
没怎么的，闹着玩
I heard Lu Wenzhong slept with her.
我听说卢文仲把她给睡了
Is that real or fake?
真的假的？
What's so rare about sleeping with her?
睡她有啥可稀奇的？
President Lu has slept with countless girls like her.
就她这样的 卢总都不知道睡了多少个了
Just standard bedroom business.
不就床上那些事嘛
Well, she sure puts on a convincing act.
那她装得可挺像
Sitting right there, looking like an angel.
往那一坐，跟个仙女似的
Never expected that what I lost was already...
没料到我所失的竟已…
...everything I owned.
是我的所有
Is there a problem?
有什么事情啊？
Little kid.
小朋友
Were you the one who touched Shen Mo?
是不是你动的沈墨？
So you're her little boyfriend.
原来你就是她那个小男朋友啊
Quite a handsome guy.
帅哥呀
But your head doesn't seem too sharp.
但你的脑袋看起来不是很灵活的啊
Go back and tell Miss Shen...
回去告诉沉小姐
...choosing a man isn't just about good looks.
选男人不能光看脸的
What the fuck are you doing?
你他妈干啥呢？
You bastard!
混蛋
Fuck, am I giving you too much face?
他妈的，我是不是给你脸了你啊？
My... my apologies, President Lu.
不…不好意思，卢总
He went crazy all of a sudden.
抽风了这是
Handsome.
帅哥
Do you know how much this suit costs?
你知道我这身西装多少钱吗？
12,000 yuan.
一万两千块
Looks pretty sharp on me, doesn't it?
我穿起来很帅吧？
But on you, it would look like a clown outfit.
但你穿就会像小丑
People choose clothes...
人选衣服
...and clothes choose people too.
衣服也要选人的
Find something that fits your level.
找个合适自己的
- Drag him out.
- Move it.
-整出去
-走
I... I'll be back in a bit.
我…我一会过来啊
Bring a fruit platter to this room!
来，给这屋端点果盘来
Come on... just a minor scene.
来…小场面了
See it all the time.
经常见啊
- Come on... don't let it spoil our fun.
- Cheers...
-来…不要扫我们的兴啊
-来…
Alright...
行…
Did I hire you to come here and chase girls?
我雇你来是让你搞对象来的啊？
Don't come back again.
以后别来了
Watch him, don't let him back inside.
看着他，不让他进来
You dared curse at me!
让你骂我
Go ahead, curse now!
你倒骂呀
Still cursing?
骂不骂了？
Where's Shen Mo?
沈墨呢？
Sui Dong...
隋东
Sui Dong was rushed to the hospital.
隋东送医院了
The three of us must be the unluckiest people in the world.
咱们仨应该是世界上 最倒楣的人了吧？
The unlucky ones should be them.
倒楣的应该是他们
Step back, step back...
来，往后退…